Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Infiltration
Episode 54
Wolffy, are you nervous?
With you by my side, I’m not nervous.
Don’t worry, Wolnie.
I’ll be keeping an eye on this restoration device for Wolffy.
Besides, it was developed by Mr. Slowy,
so it’s sure to be fine.
I just need to input a bit more data,
and then we can start your restoration, Wolffy.
This is the real-time feed from the drone.
I never expected that Blue would obtain the Absorption Device
and not use it to save the original world,
but rather to establish a so-called “new world”.
How could this happen?
Is this his method of saving the world?
This place is just a patchwork creation.
How is this any different from a bandit?
Before he absorbs all the energy,
we need to take action immediately.
Mr. Slowy, what can we do?
Based on the footage captured by the drones earlier,
the core device has already been integrated into Blue’s world.
And now we can see
that a lot of energy from his world is merging into this energy shield
so by following this energy, we can definitely find the Absorption Device
But what does that have to do with saving Weslie?
If Weslie was sucked in while wearing the Energization Prevention Device
then as long as we follow this energy
we’re bound to run into him
But
it looks like this energy shield
isn’t something you can just enter easily
You’re smart
You grasped the key point right away
Seems like anyone named Sparky is pretty smart.
He doesn’t seem to have anything to do with you, though.
This energy shield seems to exist to protect his world.
If we want to get in,
we’ll have to blast a small opening.
Go to this spot here;
it’s the shortest route.
Let’s make it quick.
Now that we know the mission, it’s simple.
Let’s move out.
Hold on.
Blue is so cautious;
he’s bound to have guards posted.
Right, that’s what I was thinking too.
So, what can we do?
I suggest we split into two groups.
One group goes in first
to draw the enemy away
and open a passage in the energy shield.
The other group waits for the shield to open
then rushes inside
to join Weslie in destroying the device.
Weslie usually handles this kind of thing.
I never thought it would be my turn—Sparky’s turn—today.
Like I said, he isn’t you.
That sounds like a good plan.
But let’s try to operate covertly.
We’ll act as the vanguard, then.
Me again?
I’ll go too.
Safety first, kids.
Leave the security here to us.
Good luck.
Once I’ve restored,
I’ll come help you right away.
Why did Mr. Slowy only have the drones drop us off here?
There are very few drones left.
Mr. Slowy is saving them for the next assault team.
As soon as we break the energy shield,
Tibbie and the others will storm inside at top speed.
Fair enough.
It turns out anyone named Sparky is really smart.
There are so many residents here.
If they spot us, they might tell Blue.
We need to be careful.
Stick close to me, Paddi.
This is the Thorn Forest.
He really can piece anything together.
Watch this.
How is that possible?
We’ll help too.
Why are these thorns so hard?
It’s metal from the Blue Planet world.
It’s a bit troublesome when elements from different worlds are mixed together.
This is the only way to the energy shield.
We can’t take a detour.
Come take a look at this.
There are some parts here that aren’t made of metal.
Let’s attack this spot together.
I can handle this myself.
I thought you were just a bit smart,
but I didn’t expect your abilities to be this impressive, too.
We’re almost there.
Just hang in there a little longer.
It looks like Blue didn’t even post any guards.
He’s not that smart after all.
Watch out!
This is…
Brown, weren’t you…by Blue…
Brown, it’s me.
It’s Sparky.
What on earth happened to you?
Fight back!
He isn’t our enemy.
The fact that he’s attacking you without holding back
only proves that right now,
he’s being controlled by Blue.
Here he comes.
If we can’t beat him, can’t we at least dodge him?
Brown is under Blue’s control.
We’d better be careful.
Let’s make a run for the energy shield while we can.
It’s no use hiding anywhere.
Run!
What are you standing there for? Get in.
It’s a good thing we’ve been to Blue Planet World before.
The roads are pretty much the same.
We should have shaken him off by now.
With my driving skills,
you can rest easy.
Don’t even think about getting close to that place.
We’ll hold him off.
Paddi, look for a chance to run.
But…
Sparky is right.
We’re out of time—go!
Today…
None of you can leave this place.
Don’t forget about me.
I can’t hold on much longer.
I’ll help you.
Paddi, go!
You guys…
Hurry, go!
I understand; I will definitely complete the mission.
Watch out!
Sparky!
Almost at the energy shield.
Where do you think you’re going?
Green, you’ve been controlled by Blue too?
A cheap trick.
Why is this happening?
Don’t waste your energy.
No matter what…
I can’t give up.
My world is still waiting for me to save it.
You can even fuse?
Do you think that’ll work?
I thought I’d run into a challenging opponent.
I didn’t expect you to be this weak.
You’re not even a proper warm-up for me.
So, you really are being controlled.
The Green I know…
wouldn’t say things like that.
But…
you’re not wrong.
To even make it this far,
I’ve had to rely on Sparky and the others.
But they’re all saving the world in their own way.
Weslie is still in there, waiting for us to rescue him.
So…
Why are there still more?
No matter how powerful you are,
I’ll fight to the end in my own way.
Pulling a cheap trick like that…
Explode!
It worked.
Now I need to lure him away
so Tibbie and Jonie can get inside safely.
I’m going to call my friends over.
I’m running!
Don’t run!
Tibbie, Jonie—it’s up to you guys now.
Sparky and the others succeeded.
It’s time for us to go.
Be careful, kids.
To be continued